{
    "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pada present simple, past simple, present cont, dan past cont!:)",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Simple Present Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncall my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am called by my best friend<br>Simple Past Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncalled my friend yesterday\n<br>\n-Passive :\nI was called by my best friend yesterday\n\n<br>Present\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nam calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am being called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Past\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nwas calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI was being called by my best friend\n\n<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buat-karangan-3-paragraf-tentang-profesi-guru-dlm-bahasa-inggris-159",
            "question": "Buat karangan 3 paragraf tentang profesi guru dlm bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<strong>Why God Made TeachersBy Kevin William Huff</strong><br>When God created teachers,\u00a0He gave us special friends\u00a0To help us understand His world\u00a0And truly comprehend\u00a0The beauty and the wonder\u00a0Of everything we see,\u00a0And become a better person\u00a0With each discovery.\u00a0<br>When God created teachers,\u00a0He gave us special guides\u00a0To show us ways in which to grow\u00a0So we can all decide\u00a0How to live and how to do\u00a0What&#039;s right instead of wrong,\u00a0To lead us so that we can lead\u00a0And learn how to be strong.\u00a0<br>Why God created teachers,\u00a0In His wisdom and His grace,\u00a0Was to help us learn to make our world\u00a0<span>A better, wiser place.</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tulislahlah-100-kata-benda-noun-lengkap-dengan-artinya-470",
            "question": "Tulislahlah 100 kata benda (noun) lengkap dengan artinya!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "\u2013 account \u2013 artinya: rekening, akun <br> \u2013 achiever \u2013 yang berprestasi <br> \u2013 acoustics \u2013 akustik <br> \u2013 action \u2013 tindakan <br> \u2013 activity \u2013 aktivitas <br> \u2013 actor \u2013 aktor, bintang film untuk laki <br> \u2013 addition \u2013 tambahan <br> \u2013 adjustment \u2013 pengaturan <br> \u2013 advertisement \u2013 iklan <br> \u2013 advice \u2013 nasihat <br> \u2013 aftermath \u2013 buntut <br> \u2013 afternoon \u2013 sore <br> \u2013 afterthought \u2013 renungan <br> \u2013 agreement \u2013 perjanjian <br> \u2013 air \u2013 udara <br> \u2013 airplane \u2013 pesawat terbang <br> \u2013 airport \u2013 bandara <br> \u2013 alarm \u2013 alarm <br> \u2013 alley \u2013 gang <br> \u2013 amount \u2013 jumlah <br> \u2013 amusement \u2013 hiburan <br> \u2013 anger \u2013 kemarahan <br> \u2013 angle \u2013 sudut <br> \u2013 animal \u2013 hewan <br> \u2013 answer adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: jawaban<br>- ant \u2013 artinya: semut <br> \u2013 ants \u2013 banyak semut<br> \u2013 apparatus \u2013 aparat <br> \u2013 apparel \u2013 pakaian <br> \u2013 apple \u2013 apel <br> \u2013 apples \u2013 apel bentuk jamak<br> \u2013 appliance \u2013 alat <br> \u2013 approval \u2013 persetujuan <br> \u2013 arch \u2013 lengkungan <br> \u2013 argument \u2013 argumen <br> \u2013 arithmetic \u2013 hitungan<br> \u2013 arm \u2013 lengan <br> \u2013 army \u2013 tentara <br> \u2013 art \u2013 seni <br> \u2013 attack \u2013 serangan<br> \u2013 attempt \u2013 usaha <br> \u2013 attention \u2013 perhatian <br> \u2013 attraction \u2013 daya tarik <br> \u2013 aunt \u2013 bibi <br> \u2013 authority \u2013 kewenangan <br> \u2013 babies \u2013 bayi <br> \u2013 baby \u2013 bayi <br> \u2013 back \u2013 kembali <br> \u2013 badge \u2013 lencana <br> \u2013 bag adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: tas<br>- bait \u2013 artinya: umpan <br> \u2013 balance \u2013 keseimbangan<br> \u2013 ball \u2013 bola <br> \u2013 balloon \u2013 balon <br> \u2013 balls \u2013 bola <br> \u2013 banana \u2013 pisang <br> \u2013 band \u2013 pita <br> \u2013 base \u2013 dasar <br> \u2013 baseball \u2013 baseball <br> \u2013 basin \u2013 cekungan <br> \u2013 basket \u2013 keranjang <br> \u2013 basketball \u2013 bola basket <br> \u2013 bat \u2013 kelelawar <br> \u2013 bath \u2013 mandi <br> \u2013 battle \u2013 pertempuran <br> \u2013 bead \u2013 titis <br> \u2013 beam \u2013 balok <br> \u2013 bean \u2013 kacang <br> \u2013 bear \u2013 beruang <br> \u2013 bears \u2013 beruang <br> \u2013 beast \u2013 binatang <br> \u2013 bed \u2013 tempat tidur <br> \u2013 bedroom \u2013 kamar tidur <br> \u2013 beds \u2013 ranjang <br> \u2013 bee adalah kata benda (noun) dalam bahasa Inggris berarti: lebah <br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "book=buku<br>table=meja<br>chair=kursi<br>pillow=bantal<br>knife=pisau<br>cupboard=lemari<br>desk=meja belajar<br>door=pintu<br>eraser=penghapus<br>pencil=pensil<br>pen=pulpen<br>marker=spidol<br>whiteboard=papan tulis putih<br>blackboard=papan tulis hitam<br>window=jendela<br>apple=apel<br>bike=sepeda<br>bed=kasur<br>flag=bendela<br>board=papan<br>wood=kayu<br>pencil case=tempat pensil<br>bag=tas<br>pouch=tas kecil<br>shoe=sepatu<br>sandals=sandal<br>computer=komputer<br>paper=kertas<br>floor=lantai<br>cloth=baju<br>skirt=rok<br>short=celana pendek<br>trouser=celana panjang<br>trash=tempat sampah<br>crap=sampah<br>dust=debu<br>wardrobe=tempat baju<br>map=peta<br>globe=bola dunia<br>clock=jam<br>wall=tembok<br>fence=pagar<br>blanket=selimut<br>aduh apa itu udah 100?capek ngetik nih",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalau-nama-lain-dari-v1-v2-v3-dan-ving-apa-701",
            "question": "Kalau nama lain dari V1, V2, V3, dan Ving apa?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 : bare infintive<br>v2 : past tense<br>v3: past participle<br>ve/es : additional infinitive<br>ving : present participle<br><br>maksudnya ini ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-kalimat-dari-kata-punishment-945",
            "question": "Buat kalimat dari kata punishment",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "the teacher gave punishment to the students who didn&#039;t do homework<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>criminals were punishment because they stole goods belonging to <span>citizens</span></span>.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "persamaan-simple-past-amp-present-perfect-695",
            "question": "Persamaan simple past &amp; present perfect",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "sama sama merupakan absolute relative tenses dimana sebuah kalimat terdiri dari lebih dari satu keterangan waktu.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "sama-sama menceritakan tentang masa lampau<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-naskah-drama-komedi-b-inggris-dengan-pemeran-5-atau-6-or-399",
            "question": "Buatlah naskah drama komedi b. inggris dengan pemeran 5 atau 6 orang!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span><span>Naughty Rat - Rat - Drama Script<br><br></span>The atmosphere in front of the school on an afternoon after school . <span>Seen a school kid named Derrick bought some peanuts from a bag shop .<br><br></span><span>He soon returned to rumahnya.Anting Pendan Swarovski Crystals 3D Dome AKS10<br><br></span>Deri home atmosphere . Deri opened his shoes and socks . He just put it in the back door of his house . He then immediately went to his room . <span>His mother saw action Deri .<br><br></span>Mother : ( angry ) \" Derrick , do not put your shoes carelessly . <span>Kan , already the mother provide special shelf for storing shoes . \"<br><br></span>Derrick : ( wiping sweat from his brow ) \" right Deri tired , Mom . Today its sultry taste really. <span>Anyway , right there Surti Bi . \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Bi Surti returned home for three days . <span>Anyway , why do you ask Bi Surti ? \"<br><br></span><span>Deri \" Surti Bi Usually it is like clearing my shoes . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( annoyed ) \" For something like this , you could sense Mrs. ngerjakannya own . \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( immediately took his shoes and socks that had a jumble ) \" Aahh ... Mom . \"<br><br></span>Deri immediately went into his room . Atmosphere of the room changed to Deri . In the room , there is a small bed , a fan , a desk , and a trash can . Deri lay down on his bed . He threw his bag to the side under the desk. He had not changed his uniform . <span>Then , he turned on the fan.<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( while reading a book that he takes from the desk study ) \" Ahh ... so it better .... \"<br><br></span>Deri unwrapping beans that he bought earlier. <span>He opened one by one and just throw peanut shells under his bed .<br><br></span>Atmosphere of the night . Derrick could not sleep . <span>He heard strange noises .<br><br></span>Ciiitttt ... cit ... cittt .... Deri fear . <span>From under his bed , out of a rat .<br><br></span>Deri shocked . He is most afraid of mice . Not long ago , few rats out from under his bed . <span>Derrick took the broom fibers .<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( trying to repel the rats ) \" Ukhhh ... disturb it! \" ( Hit a rat )<br><br></span><span>Some rats even approached Deri .<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( scared and screaming ) \" Mommy, Mommy tolongin Derrick ! \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( opening the room door Deri ) \"What you really shout ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( pale face ) \" Mother , many si Jerry ! \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : \" Jerry , who &#039;s Jerry ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( pointing under his bed ) \" mean Deri many small rodents . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( confused ) \"Where ? \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : \" It was under the bed Deri !<br><br></span>Deri fear . <span>Derrick does not want to sleep in the room Deri . \"<br><br></span><span>Mother : \"Well , tonight you&#039;re sleeping with your sister alone . \"<br><br></span>Atmosphere the morning . <span>Mom came into the room<br><br></span>Deri . <span>He was surprised to see garbage strewn under the bed Deri .<br><br></span><span>Mother : ( shouting , his face sullen )<br><br></span><span>\" Derii ... here ! \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( wearing school uniform ) \" Yes what is it , Mom ? \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Look ! \" ( Pointing to garbage strewn ) \" You slob all. <span>No wonder a lot of rats in your room . \"<br><br></span><span>Derrick : ( embarrassed and downcast ) \" Out of what , then? \"<br><br></span>Mother : \" Well anyway, even asked . From now on you have to maintain the cleanliness of your room . You do not throw litter again . <span>Kan , already the mother provide the trash in your room ( pointing to the trash ) .<br><br></span><span>What needs to be Mom made \u200b\u200bsignpost warning here ? \"<br></span>Derrick : \"I could have been . <span>Deri promise not to throw litter again .<br></span><span>Deri cured at the Jerry - Jerry naughty . \"<br></span>Mother : ( smiles ) \" Well, now you go to school . <span>After school , you must clean up your room . \"<br></span><span>Derrick : \" Well , Mom ! \"<br></span><span>Since then , Derrick always maintain the cleanliness of his room .</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-lawan-kata-dari-diligent-generous-friendly-easy-going-cre-436",
            "question": "apa lawan kata dari diligent, generous, friendly, easy-going, creative, two-faced, rebellious, aloof ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Diligent &gt;&lt; Lazy<br>Generous &gt;&lt; Stingy<br>Friendly &gt;&lt; Unfriendly, Hostile<br>Creative &gt;&lt; Uncreative<br>Two-faced &gt;&lt; Honest, Sincere<br>Rebellious &gt;&lt; Obedient, Docile<br>Aloof &gt;&lt; Friendly, Sociable",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-expression-of-plan-804",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog expression of plan...",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Nancy :hai, Nan....<br>Arum : hai,,,<br>Nancy : Rum, I have a plan to our class in this holiday,<br>Arum : hmmm, what?<br>Nancy : We will go to Amri&#039;s home, his home at highlands, how? are you agree with me?<br>Arum : I agree, we must tell our classmate ,,,<br>Nancy : Yes, when?<br>Arum : faster is better<br>Nancy : yeh...<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-naskah-drama-bahasa-inggris-untuk-7-orang-cewek-4-orang-581",
            "question": "buatkan Naskah drama bahasa inggris untuk 7 orang. cewek 4 orang, cwok 3 orang....\r\ntolong :)\u00a0 bebas, tpi jangan pnjng.panjang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Kiki: Hello,Good Morning all\nTerusin Aja yah Tema nasjah englus itu yg bagus best friend in my heart",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "create-dialogs-based-on-the-situations-below-situations-1-you-a-323",
            "question": "Create dialogs based on the situations below    situations 1 : you are at farewell party at your school. a friend has just finished singing a song well. you offer compliment to her. and she rejects the compliment. what do you and your friend say?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>me\u00a0 : your song was so amazing <br>him : thank you again <br>me\u00a0 : we&#039;ll split up .... <br>him : yes ... but I hope we&#039;ll meet again someday <br>me\u00a0 : I too ..... <br>him : I&#039;ll see you again, you have to promise we will meet again <br>me\u00a0 : yea ... I promise you, and someday we will meet again</span><br><br>arti:<br>aku : lagumu tadi sangat menakjubkan<br>dia\u00a0 : terima kasih kembali<br>aku : kita akan berpisah....<br>dia\u00a0 : ya...tapi aku harap kita akan bertemu lagi suatu saat nanti<br>aku : aku juga.....<br>dia\u00a0 : sampai jumpa lagi,kau harus berjanji kita akan bertemu lagi<br>aku : ya...aku berjanji,dan suatu saat nanti kita bakal ketemu lagi<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}